GOD IS STILL SAYING SOMETHING
On Sunday, the 28th of July 2013, Prophet T.B. Joshua gave a prophetic message concerning an Asian nation -
warning them of an incident, involving a large aircraft, carrying over 200 people,
developing a fault soon after take off.
He subsequently prayed for the nation.
These were his words:
In Jesus Christ' name.
We have to pray!
This is an Asian country.
I will not mention any country but God showed me the country.
I am seeing a very big balloon.
What is the cause of this?
It was just about to take off and the fault started.
It means that they can discover it on the tarmac but because of impatience.
If God gives me the grace, I will send a letter to the embassy of the country.
Check your airlines in your country,
It is going to be huge - almost 200 people inside.
What happened here?
It is the fault of impatience
because there are many things they need to look into before they take off
but they are unable.
What is the cause?
Two hundred people are inside the plane.
This is an Asian country.
We are going to pray for them and I will see what I can do
to send a letter to the embassy and let them know
that they should inspect any plane on their tarmac before it moves.
Take cognisance, take note so that they can avert this.
In Jesus Christ' name.
CNN BREAKING NEWS
Welcome back. Turning once again to our breaking news.
A Malaysian Airlines flight carrying nearly 240 people
has been missing for nearly 9 hours now.
Flight MH370 left Kuala Lumpur around 2:40 in the morning on its way to Beijing.
It disappeared from the radar about 2 hours later.
The CEO of Malaysian Airlines just wrapped up a news conference.
He said that he doesn't know where the plane is.
He said that there were at least fourteen nationalities represented among the passengers on board.
The airline is now notifying the next of kin.
Welcome back to our coverage. I'm Natalie Allen at CNN's center.
Two Chinese rescue ships are now on their way
to help search for the missing Malaysian Airlines jet carrying 239 people.
Chinese and Vietnamese media quoting a Vietnamese Navy Officer are now saying
that the flight crashed near Tho Chu Island.
The Boeing 777 was travelling from Kuala Lumpur to Beijing
where traffic controllers in Vietnam lost contact with it.
The Boeing 777 was travelling as we said from Kuala Lumpur.
The airline officials say that there was no distress call from the plane.
They say it was carrying seven and a half hours worth of fuel
which most certainly would have been gone by now.
Flight MH370 was due to have landed in Beijing at 6:30 local time on Saturday morning.
Our David McKenzie who is in Beijing said that the relatives have now been taken to a nearby hotel.
We believe that you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances, sermons and testimonies
from The Synagogue Church of All Nations.
Emmanuel TV - Changing Lives, Changing Nations, and Changing the World.